<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on Oshin Katulkar</title>
    <link>https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on Oshin Katulkar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Oshin Katulkar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Impact in Rural India</title>
      <link>https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/india2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/india2022/</guid>
      <description>India2022 is a business-led coalition committed to leverage the power of collaboration to unlock future-fit growth opportunities in India. Many corporates (Aditya Birla Group, Shell, GE, Cyient, Mahindra etc.) are partners in the coalition working in the areas of energy, waste and sanitation,sustainable mining and healthcare diagnostics.
Partners under India2022 are collectively working to understand and bring together key elements required to accelerate rural growth. Efforts are expected to lead to scalable commercial opportunities that demonstrate social and environmental return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Student’s Space Challenge</title>
      <link>https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/nssc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oshinkatulkar.com/portfolio/nssc/</guid>
      <description>National Students&amp;rsquo; Space Challenge (NSSC)](https://www.nssc.in/) is India&amp;rsquo;s first and largest space technology fest conducted by Space Technology Student&amp;rsquo;s Society at Indian Institute of Technology Kharagpur. The intent of the fest is to inculcate a culture of space technology, inspire research in the field of space technology, and provide a platform to explore interests in the field of space technology.
- Co-founded India’s first space technology festival for the student community with a participation of 600+ students every year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>